myeecu.org 2015-11-06

# FACTS

                                                                                                                    Rev 8/2015
                                                                                                         Privacy Notice
                   WHAT DOES EDUCATIONAL EMPLOYEES CREDIT UNION
FACTS              DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
Why?               Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers
                   the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share,
                   and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
What?              The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with
                   us. This information can include:
                        Social Security Number and income
                        Transaction history and account balances
                        Credit history and account transactions
                   When you are no longer our member, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.
How?               All financial companies need to share members’ personal information to run their everyday business. In
                   the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their members’ personal
                   information; the reasons Educational Employees Credit Union chooses to share; and whether you can
                   limit this sharing.
 Reasons we can share your personal information                 Does EECU share?              Can you limit this sharing?
For our everyday business purposes –
such as to process your transactions, maintain your
                                                                         Yes                                No
account(s), respond to court orders and legal
investigations, or report to credit bureaus
For our marketing purposes –
                                                                         Yes                                No
to offer our products and services to you
For joint marketing with other financial
                                                                         No                           We do not share
companies
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes –
                                                                         No                           We do not share
information about your transactions and experiences
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes –
                                                                         No                           We do not share
information about your creditworthiness
For non-affiliates to market to you                                      No                           We do not share
Questions? Call (800) 538-3328 or (559) 437-7700 or go to www.myEECU.org

Page 2
Who we are
Who is providing this notice?           Educational Employees Credit Union
What we do
How does EECU protect                   To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use
my personal information?                security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer
                                        safeguards and secured files and buildings.
How does EECU collect                   We collect your personal information, for example, when you:
my personal information?
                                            Open an account
                                            Apply for a loan
                                            Use your credit or debit card
                                            Make deposits or withdrawals from your account
                                            Give us your contact information
Why can’t I limit all sharing?          Federal law gives you the right to limit only:
                                            Sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes – information about your
                                            creditworthiness
                                            Affiliates from using your information to market to you
                                            Sharing for non-affiliates to market to you
                                        State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.
Definitions
Affiliates                              Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and
                                        nonfinancial companies.
                                            EECU has no affiliates.
Non-affiliates                          Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and
                                        nonfinancial companies.
                                            EECU does not share with non-affiliates so they can market to you.
Joint marketing                         A formal agreement between non-affiliated financial companies that together market
                                        financial products or services to you.
                                            EECU does not market products or services jointly with non-affiliated
                                          companies.*
Other Important Information
 *When we let you know of a financial product or service offered by another company, we retain control of your information
 until you authorize its release by choosing to become a customer of the company or by requesting their product or service.
